(no audio)
("Since U Been Gone" by Kelly Clarkson)
♪ Here's the thing we
started out friends ♪
♪ It was cool but it was all pretend ♪
♪ Yeah yeah ♪
♪ Since you been gone ♪
♪ You're dedicated you took the time ♪
♪ Wasn't long 'til I called you mine ♪
♪ Yeah yeah ♪
♪ Since you been gone ♪
♪ And all you'd ever hear me say ♪
♪ Is how I picture me with you ♪
♪ That's all you'd ever hear me say ♪
♪ But since you been gone ♪
♪ I can breathe for the first time ♪
♪ I'm so moving on yeah yeah ♪
♪ Thanks to you ♪
♪ Now I get what I want ♪
♪ Since you been gone ♪
♪ How can I put it ♪
♪ You put me on ♪
♪ I even fell for that stupid love song ♪
♪ Yeah yeah ♪
♪ Since you been gone ♪
♪ How come I'd never hear you say ♪
♪ I just wanna be with you ♪
♪ Guess you never felt that way ♪
♪ But since you been gone ♪
♪ I can breathe for the first time ♪
♪ I'm so moving on yeah yeah ♪
♪ Thanks to you ♪
♪ Now I get I get what I want ♪
♪ Since you been gone ♪
♪ You had your chance you blew it ♪
♪ Out of sight out of mind ♪
♪ Shut your mouth I just can't take it ♪
♪ Again and again and again and again ♪
("Since U Been Gone" continues)
♪ Since you been gone
since you been gone ♪
♪ I can breathe for the first time ♪
♪ I'm so moving on yeah yeah ♪
♪ Thanks to you thanks to you ♪
♪ Now I get I get what I want ♪
♪ I can breathe for the first time ♪
♪ I'm so moving on yeah yeah ♪
♪ Thanks to you thanks to you ♪
♪ Now I get I get ♪
♪ You should know you should know ♪
♪ That I get I get what I want ♪
♪ Since you been gone ♪